Dibya Ranjan **Bhoi**

SENIOR UI DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Bengaluru India



+91 8093997289



dibyabhoidibya@gmail.com

FIND ME ON

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/dibya-ranjanbhoi/

Hackerrank

hackerrank.com/DibyaRB

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT

SAP UI5

REACT

NODE.JS

ADOBE XD

HTML5

HOBBIES

TRAVELLING

PHOTOGRAPHY

COMPETITIVE **PROGRAMMING**

ABOUT ME

An UI Developer with 5 years of experience in building responsive Javascript Applications with an uncanny drive and passion to deliver User Interfaces that translate into sophisticated and aesthetically pleasing product experiences. My objective is to design and deliver end-to-end applications that balance business goals, user needs, and technological realities.

EXPERIENCE

SAP Labs India [2016 - Present]

Sept 2020 - Present

Currently working as an UI Developer for Freight Collaberation team, building interactive User Interfaces for Freight Tracking and Management, Gate Check-in and Check-out, and Dock Appointment

Scheduling processes.

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

Revamped and ovehauled the User Interface for Alerting UI as per latest industry standard UX guidelines. Worked as an UI developer for Material

Traceability team.

Feb 2018 - Dec 2019

Worked as an UI developer for Digital Compliance Platform Development Team. Created a centralized dashboard that houses multiple other applications such as Master Data Management, User Managerment, Connection Management and Metering UI also, worked as an UI Developer for Digital Compliance Services Russia Team. Devel oped Business to Business (B2B) and Business to Government (B2G) UI Applications for exchange of e-invoices, which included electronic signing of

Dec 2017 - Jan 2018

Developed and deployed a Customized ready Portal System for customers of Odisha Mining Corporation on SAP Cloud Platform. Developed various UI Applications related to Finance, Stock-

Overview

Jul 2017 - Nov 2017

Developed custom applications for S/4 HANA on Cloud Dev Team and integrated them with existing services on Fiori Cloud Portal for Creation and Approval of Business Partners using SAP Cloud Platform Workflow Service. Developed multiple overview applications for Sales Orders,

Sales Quotations, Purchase Orders.

Oct 2016 - June 2017

Worked for various clients of SAP Labs such as Wipro Technologies Bangalore, Finolex Pipes, Pune, Infosys Limited, Bangalore and Godrej Industries, Mumbai. Refined and refocused multiple existing User Interfaces, provided trainings, as well as resolved multiple issues and developed newer interfaces for various custom

use cases and analytics.

EDUCATION

2012-2016

B.tech in Computer Science and Engineering

KIIT University, CGPA 8.85

2010 - 2012

AISSCE

Mothers Public School, Percentage 89%

2005 - 2010

Higher Secondary Examination Sri Satya Sai Vidya Vihar, GPA 9.2